Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 10. Judaica, 1937 - 2007; 45 boxes
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 - 1993 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992, 1997 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 - 1993 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 2 in C Minor -- Record sleeve, undated (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2006 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 - 2001 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 - 1992 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2001 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 2002 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 - 2002 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2002 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2002 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - David Sylvester -- Obituaries, 2001 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 1998 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 - 1989, 1997 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 - 2003 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 - 2002 (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - Judaica (2 of 2), 1986 - 1998 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - "Barthes, Deconst" (2 of 2) (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - E. H. Gombrich, 2001 - 2002 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Collected images of famous Jewish people (2 of 2), 1996 - 1998 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Untitled -- miscellaneous (6 of 8), Undated. (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Untitled -- miscellaneous (7 of 8), Undated. (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Untitled -- miscellaneous (8 of 8) (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Einstein (2 of 2), 2000 - 2004 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - T.S. Elliot (2 of 2), 1996 - 2001 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Balthus (3 of 4), 1998 - 2002 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Balthus (4 of 4), 2001 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Various Artists -- articles and clippings (2 of 2) (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 3), 1971 - 2007 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Articles and Reviews -- Psychoanalysis (3 of 3), 1990 - 2006 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Reviews -- Israel and Palestine (2 of 3), 2003 - 2007 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Reviews -- Israel and Palestine (3 of 3) (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Susan Sontag -- Annotated articles, 2001 - 2005 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Philip Roth -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 2005 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Harold Bloom -- Annotated articles, 1982 - 2005 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Sigmund Freud -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 2006 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Simon Wiesenthal -- Annotated articles (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Frank Lloyd/Rothko, 1973 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Color poster with map: Sephardi Jewry in 1492", 1992 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1983 - 2003 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1992 - 2006 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Armand Hammer (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1974, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - George Gershwin -- Annotated articles, 1998 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Armand Hammer -- Articles, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1997 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 1998 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1998 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Map of Jerusalem, 1972 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Calendar (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1990 - 1997 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1991 - 1996 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Jesus -- Annotated articles (3 of 3), 1999 - 2006 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Primo Levi -- Annotated articles (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - Crash -- Film review, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Saul Bellow -- Annotated articles (2 of 2), 2000, 2005 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Marcel Proust (3 of 3), 2000 - 2002 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Mark Rothko -- Annotated articles, 1998 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - "The Pope's in a Confessional, and Jews Are Listening" by Celestine Bohlen, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Isadore Twersky -- obituary, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Film -- annotated articles, Undated. (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous articles, Undated. (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Larry Rivers -- Obituaries, 2002 (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - "Behind a Century of Photos, Was There a Jewish Eye?" by Richard B. Woodward, 2002 (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 2002 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1993, 2001 - 2002 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 2001 - 2002 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Isaiah Berlin -- Annotated articles (5 of 5), 1997 - 2001 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Elias Canetti -- Annotated articles (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 2000 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1993, 2005 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2004 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2003 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - Blum: From power to prison by Roy Jenkins, 17 November 1973 (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1996 - 1999 (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1985 - 2001 (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 2007 (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 234, Folder 15)
    - Melton Research Center for Jewish Education, 1990 - 1991 (Box 234, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 1999 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 - 1998 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 - 1999 (Box 235, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 235, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 - 1989 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 - 1993 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Fraenkel Gallery, 2001 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 1998 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Sergei Eisenstein, 1998 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 16)
    - George Solti, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 236, Folder 19)
    - George Steiner (Box 236, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 - 1993 (Box 236, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000 - 2001 (Box 236, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 2002 (Box 236, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 236, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 - 1999 (Box 236, Folder 26)
    - Baseball, 2001 - 2002 (Box 236, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 - 2002 (Box 236, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 - 1998 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 - 1989 (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 - 2000 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Art
    - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - A Singular Vision: Drawings and Paintings by Bernard Meninsky -- exhibit materials, 2001 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 2001 (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - Monica Bohm-Duchen -- photocopies of articles, 1987 - 1991 (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 - 1988 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - The Harry N. Abrams Family Collection -- exhibit brochure, 1966 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949 - 1983 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - The Israel Museum, Jerusalem -- Newsletters, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - "Meyer Schapiro: 'A Passion to Know and Make Known'" by Helen Epstein, May 1983 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - "On Abstraction in Painting" by Avigdor Arikha -- Draft, undated (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - The Jewish Museum by Cecil Roth, 1933 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 - 1985 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Coat of Many Colors: Pages from a Jewish Life by Israel Shenker, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - In the Flower of Youth: Maurycy Gottlieb 1856-1879, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Clement Greenberg -- essays, 1962, undated (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Emily Mason: Recent Paintings, 2007; 1 item. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2005 - 2007 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Archie Rand: Had Gadya -- keepsake and invitation, 2007 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Ben Tritt: Recent Paintings, 2007 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2007 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Judy Chicago: Jewish Identity, 2007 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Stephen Finer -- brochure and invitation, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Glenn Sujo: A Cabinet of Drawings, 2006 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 2006 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Archie Rand: Had Gadya -- photographs, undated; 10 items. (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Archie Rand: Had Gadya -- photographs, undated; 21 items. (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Announcements and invitations, 2005 - 2006 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Tom Wudl: You've Got to be Kidding!?, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Encountering the Second Commandment: An International Traveling Exhibition, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- 11. Tate Materials, 1963 - 2007; 8 boxes
  This series consists of materials related to Kitaj's Tate Retrospective and subsequent battle with critics including: catalog proofs and drafts, reviews, correspondence, and art ideas.
  - No Subseries assigned
    - "Varschreibt! Conversation in the Cemetery" (1 of 2), 1936 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - "Varschreibt! Conversation in the Cemetery" (2 of 2) (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - "J Matters" (1 of 6), 1979 - 1983 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1995 - 1996 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - "H", 1994 - 1996 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Notes and annotated articles (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - "Joe Singer Room" (1 of 2), undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - "Joe Singer Room" (2 of 2), 1983 - 1993 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective --Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Kitaj in the Aura of Cezanne and Other Masters, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - "Flora of the J's; Gulf; Riverbank" (1 of 2), 3 items. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Letters of Support, 1994, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Reviews and Critics, 1983 - 1998 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Reviews and Critics, 1990, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Tate Catalogue -- Richard Morphet Interview, 1992- 1993 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Tate Catalogue -- Prefaces (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Tate Retrospective -- Invitations, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit materials, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1994 - 1997, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Jake Auerbach -- Film (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Tate Catalogue -- Chronology compiled by Joanne Northey, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Hebrew Alphabet, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Support (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Letters of Support (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Letters of Support (3 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Tate Retrospective -- Draft of Exhibition Guide, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - "Tate War "-- Essay, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - London Magazine, 1979, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence -- "The Tate War", 1986 - 1998 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Marilyn McCully -- Letter to the Editor (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Tate Retrospective -- Photocopies of press clippings, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Tate Retrospective -- Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Sandra catalogs, 1996, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Tate Catalogue -- Marco Livingstone essay and interview, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - "Thugs", 1994 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - "Dan! Wol! Retired! Other Retired Stuff!" (1 of 2), 1989 - 1990 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - "Dan! Wol! Retired! Other Retired Stuff!" (2 of 2), 1989 - 1990 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - "Plus" (1 of 2), 1963 - 1986 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - "Classic" (1 of 3), 1980 - 1999 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - "Classic" (2 of 3) (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Exhibit materials, undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - The Independent -- Letter to the Editor, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Reviews, 1994 -1995, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Critics, 1986, 1995 - 1998 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - "Tate War" articles (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous articles (1 of 2), 1986 - 1987 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous articles (2 of 2), 1986 - 1987 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Tate Show Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991 - 1994 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Tate Show Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991 - 1994 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Tate Show Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Tate Show Correspondence (2 of 2), 1977, 1992 - 1994 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Richard Wollheim, 1993 - 1994 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Richard Wollheim, 1993 - 1994 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Friedlanders/Home Purchase, 1980 - 1986 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - "The British Library" (1 of 3) (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - LACMA controversy articles, 1992 - 1993 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Tate War -- articles and reviews, 1994 - 1997 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - "Critics", 1993 - 1999 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1964 - 2008 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - "Watch Out! Beware!" (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Critics, 1992 - 1996 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - R.B. Kitaj: An American in Vienna, 1998 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- catalogue proofs, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - R.B. Kitaj: A Retrospective -- T-shirt design, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Reviews (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Reviews, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Reviews, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - "J Matters" (3 of 6), 1977 - 1984 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - "J Matters" (4 of 6), 1977 - 1984 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - "J Matters" (5 of 6) (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - "British Library" (2 of 3), 1995 - 2007 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Annotated articles (1 of 2), 1995 - 1996 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Annotated articles (2 of 2), 1995 - 1996 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1986, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Reviews (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Reviews, 1997 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Reviews, 1996 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Letters, 1994 - 1996 (Box 190)
    - Untitled (Critics) -- oversize, Undated. (Box 191)
    - "Classic 1980" -- oversized doc box (Box 191)
    - "Mossad" -- oversized doc box, 1977 - 2004 (Box 191)
    - "Mossad" -- mag sized doc box, 1984 - 2004 (Box 192)
    - Clippings collected by Kitaj -- mag box, 1993 - 2004 (Box 192)
    - Articles about Kitaj, 1980 - 2004 (Box 192)
    - Un-German Activities --mag size (Box 192)
    - Mossad, 1984 - 2004 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - "S", Undated. (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Sandra -- catalogs, proofs (legal sized), 1996, 1994 (Box 193)
    - loose from box 56, 1995 - 1998 (Box 193)
    - Letters to editors of Independent -- in defense of Kitaj, 1994 (Box 193)
    - "Classic 1980" -- legal sized doc box, 1980 - 1999 (Box 193)
    - Untitled -- legal sized doc box, undated (Box 193)
    - "Plus" -- legal sized doc box, 1963 - 1986 (Box 193)
    - Tate catalog -- legal, 1994 (Box 193)
    - Thugs -- legal sized (Box 193)
    - Untitled (Critics) -- legal size, 1994, 1999 (Box 193)
    - Dan! Wol! Retired! Other Retired Stuff!, 1989 - 1990 (Box 193)
    - Reviews -- legal, 1994 (Box 193)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 - 1997 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 1996 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995 - 1996 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated. (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated. (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated. (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Annotated articles (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Annotated articles, 1985 - 2003 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Annotated articles (1 of 2), 1994 - 1996 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Annotated articles (2 of 2), 1994 - 1996 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Untitled red folder (2 of 2), 1995 - 1996 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Annotated articles (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Annotated articles, 1994 - 1997 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Reviews (1 of 3), 1993 - 1997 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Reviews (2 of 3), 1993 - 1997 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Reviews (3 of 3), 1993 - 1997 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Reviews (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - "British Library", 1987 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - "H! Varschreibt!", 1982 - 1990 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Publicity, 1963 - 2002 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Tate War -- articles, 1994 - 1997 (Box 226, Folder 8)
- 12. Art Sources, 1939 - 2007; 35 boxes
  This series consists of a variety of collected materials used by Kitaj as art sources including: exhibit announcements, clippings, annotated articles, photographs, sketches and notes.
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Book covers (1 of 16), Undated.; 7 items. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Book covers (2 of 16), Undated.; 5 items. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Book covers (3 of 16), Undated.; 7 items. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Book covers (4 of 16), Undated.; 5 items. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Book covers (5 of 16), Undated.; 5 items. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Book covers (6 of 16), Undated.; 7 items. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Book covers (7 of 16), Undated.; 7 items. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Book covers (8 of 16), Undated.; 6 items. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Book covers (9 of 16), Undated.; 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Book covers (10 of 16), Undated.; 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Book covers (11 of 16), Undated.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Book covers (12 of 16), Undated.; 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Book covers (13 of 16), Undated.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Book covers (14 of 16), undated; 17 items. (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Book covers (15 of 16), 1969 - 1989; 10 items. (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Book covers (16 of 16), 1988 - 1999; 14 items. (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - "J Room" (1 of 2), undated; 8 items. (Box 141)
    - Kitaj and Sandra Fisher wedding (1 of 4), 1983; 19 items. (Box 141)
    - "Books" (2 of 3), 1976 - 1980 (Box 141)
    - "Books" (1 of 3), 1979 - 1983 (Box 141)
    - "Women" (2 of 2), 1978 - 1981 (Box 141)
    - "Women" (1 of 2), 1979 - 1981 (Box 141)
    - "Jewish Writers" (1 of 2), 1982 - 1994 (Box 141)
    - "Drancy" (3 of 3), 1946; 1 item. (Box 141)
    - "Drancy" (2 of 3) (Box 141)
    - "Drancy" (1 of 3), 1983 - 1986 (Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous -- photographs and sources for pictures, 1990 - 1991 (Box 141)
    - Kitaj and Sandra Fisher wedding (4 of 4), 1983; 21 items. (Box 141)
    - Kitaj and Sandra Fisher wedding (2 of 4), 1973, 1975; 2 items. (Box 141)
    - Kitaj and Sandra Fisher wedding (3 of 4), 1983 - 1990; 27 items. (Box 141)
    - Annotated clippings, 1978 - 1992 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Abstraction-Création: art non-figuratif (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Mounted photograph, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - "S" (1 of 2), 1996; 24 items. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - "Books" (1 of 1), 1997 - 2007 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - "Movies", 1992 - 2003 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - "Nietzsche" (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - "Eliot/Wasteland" (1 of 5), 1972 - 2002 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Collection of "…ists" (1 of 3), 1996 - 2000 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - "Robert Duncan / John Ashbery" (1 of 3), 1981 - 2005 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - "Cezanne", 1978 - 1997 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - "Holocaust" (1 of 6) (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Annotated articles -- various world events, 1993 - 1994 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Annotated articles -- various artists and writers, 1990 - 1996 (Box 145, Folder 16)
    - Art notes and clippings (1 of 2), 1978 - 1997 (Box 145, Folder 17)
    - "J. Singer/Jaures Piazetta" (1 of 4), 1993 - 2002 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - "J. Singer/Jaures Piazetta" (2 of 4) (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Morocco by Vincent Monteil, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - "Kafka" (1 of 4), 1978 - 1995 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Book covers, undated; 2 items. (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - "Bacon" (2 of 3), 1992 - 2002 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - "Rembrandt" (1 of 3), 1999 - 2007 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - "Rembrandt" (2 of 3), 1933 - 2005 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - "Pound" (1 of 2), 1988 - 2004 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - "Giacometti" (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Howard Hodgkin, 1990 - 1996 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Howard Hodgkin (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - "Philosophers" (1 of 4), 1955 - 2006 (Box 151, Folder 9)